【吸血鬼日记】 前情提要
Previously on "The Vampire Diaries"...
达蒙死了
Damon's gone!
阿拉里克能抹去我所有的
Alaric will compel away any memories
关于达蒙和我在一起的记忆
I had of Damon and me being together.
泰勒和斯特凡已经走了
Tyler and Stefan are on board.
抹除吧 求你了
Just take it away, please.
吸血鬼不能进入神秘瀑布镇
Vampires can't get into Mystic Falls.
-他们能在边境埋伏 -啊
- They can lurk around the borders. - Aah!
不要
No!
卡罗琳让她忘记埃琳娜攻击了她
Caroline compelled her to forget Elena attacked her.
没有什么大不了
It's not a big deal.
你来自神秘瀑布镇么
You're from Mystic Falls?
事实上是来自其中一个创始人家族
One of the founding families actually.
有遗言吗
Any final words?
我们到底在哪儿
Where the hell are we?
1994.
我们通过魔法来到的这儿
We got here by magic.
魔法应该能把我们带离这里
Magic should be able to get us out.
看看谁填了横27行
Look who got 27 across.
-我没完成这个 -我也没有
- I didn't finish this. - Well, neither did I.
有别的人在这儿
There's someone else here.
斯特凡没有告别
Stefan didn't say good-bye.
达蒙和邦妮死了 而他就这么走了
Damon and Bonnie died, and he just left.
放开她
Let her go.
这儿不是停车场 孩子
Ain't a parking lot, kid.
是么 嗯 我不是来这儿工作的
Yeah? Well, I'm not here to work.
我要请假
Need a few days off.
看来我需要新的工作机器了
And it looks like I need a new mechanic.
我说我需要休息几天
I said I need a few days off.
你反应迟钝么
Are you slow?
简单来说
Let me simplify.
留下来 有工作 请假 就直接下岗
Stay... keep the job. Leave... lose it.
噢
Ohh!
你怎么能这么有力气
How the hell are you so strong?
你雇了个吸血鬼
You hired a vampire.
下次 记得调查员工背景
Next time, do a background check.
现在闭嘴 别动
Now shut up and don't move.
你不知道我想这么做多久了
You have no idea how long I've wanted to do that.
你看 我想要一个全新的开始
See, I was trying to get a fresh start,
有正常的生活 正常的工作 正常的混蛋老板
live a normal life, normal job, normal dick of a boss.
这个说的就是你
That's you by the way.
这个地方应该是我的庇护所
This place was supposed to be my sanctuary,
直到昨天一直是
and it was until yesterday.
跟我来
Come with me.
那是我的女朋友艾薇
That's my girlfriend Ivy.
昨天晚上有人就在我眼前杀了她
Somebody killed her last night right in front of me,
所以现在我要回家
so now I need to go back home...
我最不想去的地方
Last place on this planet I want to be...
找到他 然后杀了他
Find him, and kill him.
像我说过的 我需要请假
Like I said, I need a few days off.
你应该需要休假了
You should take a few days off.
谢了 伙计 我会的
Thanks, buddy. I will.
现在我要你开着我的车
Now I need you to drive my car
进树林里
into the woods.
你要埋了我的女友 然后忘掉发生的这一切
You're gonna bury my girlfriend and forget this ever happened.
哦对了 我回来之后 你要给我加薪
Oh, and when I get back, you're giving me a raise.
吸血鬼
第六季  第二集
日记
视频字幕由 SSK字幕组 制作发布
字幕只供学习 请勿做任何商业行为
敬请关注新浪微博@SSK字幕组
合作贴吧：吸血鬼日记吧
翻译：Krystle 小P Bunny Brian Jophy
所以 我 嗯 自愿在医院呆到 比如说 两点
So I, uh, volunteer at the hospital until, like, 2:00,
之后 我觉得我们可以拼车
and then I figure we can carpool
校对：小P Jophy
去深水湖的派对
to the party at the swimming hole.
嗯 一般你搬回来的时候会拿出你的东西
Um, normally when you move back in, you unpack.
我不打算留在这儿
I'm not staying.
昨晚只是一时的懦弱
Last night was just a momentary moment of weakness.
时轴：络睿    压制：Beloved    总监：小P
一时的
Momentary moment?
你确定你不想回学校么
Are you sure you don't want to come back to school?
卡罗琳 需要朋友并不代表着懦弱
Caroline, needing your friends isn't a weakness,
合作贴吧：吸血鬼日记吧
一时的 或是别的什么
momentary or otherwise.
对斯特凡去讲 他显然谁也不需要
Tell that to Stefan, who clearly needs no one.
给他点空间吧 他失去了哥哥
Cut him some slack. He lost his brother.
的确 他哥哥是没有灵魂的杀人狂魔
Granted, said brother was a soulless homicidal maniac,
但是血浓于水
but still.
什么
What?
没什么 只是 只是我得走了
Nothing. I just... I got to go.
我要和恩佐去吃早饭 所以
I've got breakfast with Enzo, so...
-恩佐么 -对啊
- Enzo? - Mm-hmm.
你们一起去旅行
You guys go on one road trip,
突然之间 你们一起去吃早饭
and all of a sudden, you're breakfast buddies?
对啊 我是这么想的
Yeah, I guess so.
讽刺的是 他的确已经成为了
Ironically, he's recently become
我生活中最安稳的一个人
one of the more stable people in my life.
好吧 邀请他去派对吧
Ok. Then invite him to the party.
-埃琳娜 -拜托 我有马特
- Elena. - Come on. I got Matt
不让他进行下午的训练
to take the afternoon off from his training
泰勒也要暂停球队练习
and Tyler to give the practice squad a break.
连杰里米也会来
Even Jeremy is coming.
我们真的好久没有在一起过了
It's been forever since we've all been together.
会很有趣的
It'll be fun.
别让我用核武器的强硬方式
Don't make me invoke the nuclear option.
因为我会每隔五分钟轰炸你一次
Because I will selfie bomb you every 5 minutes.
-好吧 我会去派对的 -太棒了
- Ok. Fine. I'll go to the party. - Yay!
但是我不会搬过来
But I'm not moving back in.
那个对话应该在拍广告的时候讲
That is a conversation to be had over jell-o shots.
阿拉里克对她做了什么
What did Alaric do to her?
我知道她不记得
All I know is she doesn't remember
她看到了达蒙的什么事
whatever it is she saw in Damon,
并且我们应该让过去成为过去
and we're supposed to keep it that way.
我刚刚和她度过了一整晚
I just spent the whole night with her,
感觉很奇怪
and it's weird.
她一点也不像原来的样子了
She just doesn't seem like her old self.
是的 那是因为她很快乐 这不就是关键么
Yeah. It's because she's happy. Isn't that the point?
我想是吧
I guess.
我得挂了 之后再联系
Look. I got to go. I'll see you later.
现在洗车还太早吧
It's a little early for a carwash.
是啊 我买了一些护根
Oh, yeah. I brought in some mulch
好让你们去清理四号那个小公园
so you guys could clean up that little park on 4th.
但是没想到它们留下的污渍太多了
Turns out red mulch stains.
-有谁想得到呢 -我的朋友要开派对
- Who knew? - My friends are having a party,
我想下午吃完午餐就过去
and I'd like to go by this afternoon after lunch.
你想要请假
You need a permission slip?
我又不是你老妈 去吧
I'm not your mom. Go.
带上杰 我骗他帮我洗车
And take Jay. Suckered him into washing my car.
他也想找点乐子
He needs some fun.
你开车 我喝了点酒
You're driving. I'm drinking.
你们俩都给我小心点
Both of you, keep your eyes open.
我们最近有很多人被野兽袭击了
We've had a lot of animal attacks lately.
-他是在说那个被狗咬了的女孩 -我知道
- He means dog bite girl. - Yeah. I know what he means.
洗澡间里有四个淋浴头
That shower has 4 heads.
谁这么脏得用到四个淋浴头
Who's so dirty they need 4 heads?
你别吓到了
You'd be surprised.
你想要波本酒还是 波本酒
You want bourbon or, well, bourbon?
我讨厌波本酒 但是我喜欢这个房子
I hate bourbon, but I love this house.
我能不能假装我找到了我爸爸
Can I just pretend that I found my dad
他就住在这
and it's whoever lives here?
相信我 他肯定不住在这
Trust me. It's not.
为什么 我妈之前在这个镇
Why not? My mom lived in Mystic Falls
住了好几年直到她怀上了我 有个谁让她怀孕了
for years before she had me. Somebody had to knock her up.
-你就没想过问她吗 -真是个好主意 快点
- You ever think about asking her? - Oh. Good idea. Hurry.
-我们去她的坟前问吧 -我知道了 抱歉
- Let's go to the cemetery. - Gotcha. Sorry.
-谁住在这 -两兄弟
- Who does live here anyway? - Two brothers.
一个搬走了 另一个死了
One moved. The other is dead.
-嘿 问你个问题 很快的 -快答 不行
- Hey. Quick question. - Quick answer. No.
真好笑 今天我们有个派对
Hilarious. We're having a party today.
你觉得你能在划船吧那里接到一两个桶吗
You think you could spare a keg or two from scull bar?
你可以来哦
You can come.
你 酒水 还有我哥
You and alcohol and my brother.
为什么这个组合这么熟悉又可恶呢
Why does that combination sound so familiar and terrible?
你的气管现在怎么样了 卢克
Who is your trachea, Luke?
公正的说 他道过歉了
In fairness, he apologized.
我在努力 好吗 我会控制饮酒量
I'm working on this, ok? I watch my drinking,
避开那些会让我愤怒的东西
I avoid things that make me angry.
一点钟后到吧台来 到时再看看行不行
Come by the bar after 1:00. I'll see what I can do.
你又来了
You're doing that thing again.
又来什么了
What thing?
又来当小婊砸了
Oh, the thing where you're a bitch
只因为你喜欢他
because you like somebody.
这不是显而易见的吗
It's pretty transparent.
我不怪你 他挺迷人的
I don't blame you. He's hot.
你好啊 可爱的自恋狂
Hey, cutebrag.
-你刚刚是叫我可爱的自恋狂吗 -嘿 这又不是我起的
- Did you just call me cutebrag? - Hey. I didn't come up with it.
是另外的义工
Another one of the volunteers did.
什么 有些时候你挺自恋的
What? Sometimes, you brag.
至少我有说你可爱吧
At least it has "Cute" In it.
我帮你回忆一下
Small favors.
我叫利亚姆 你叫埃琳娜
I'm Liam, you're Elena.
看 多么简单易记
See how easy it is to remember?
又在吹
Brag.
除了摧毁我的自信
Is there something you wanted other
你还想做其他什么吗
than to destroy my self-esteem?
事实上还真有
Actually, yes.
你今天下午有事吗
Are you doing anything this afternoon?
我的朋友会在我的家乡外开派对
My friends are throwing a party just outside my hometown,
有个女生我真心想介绍给你认识
and there's a girl that I actually want you to meet.
-你来就好了 -好吧
- Just come. - Ok.
斯特凡
Stefan?
嘿
Hey.
什么
What...
迄今为止 四个月没见到你
For the record, 4 months is far too long
对我来说太久了
for me to go without seeing you.
我知道 所以我来了
I know. That's why I'm here.
我过来问候一下
I wanted to stop by and say hi.
我来推吧
I got it.
好吧
Ok.
我们需要草莓 鸡蛋
We need strawberries, eggs,
牛奶 还有 蜡烛
milk, and... ooh... candles.
我知道已经过去了不短的时间
I know it's been a while,
但是你不能像坐节目那样施展魔法
but you couldn't do magic as an anchor,
所以我很好奇你是怎么认为
so I'm curious what momentary lapse of reason
你现在可以做到的
makes you think you can do it now.
刚来到这的时候 你的煎饼简直不能再难吃
You know, when all this started, you sucked at making pancakes,
但是现在至少可以放进嘴里了
and now they're somewhat edible.
牛奶 我们不能那么悲观
Milk. There's no reason to be peter pessimist.
我们已经有证据证明我们不是这里唯一的两人
We have proof we're not alone.
首先
First of all...
不要给我取昵称
Don't nickname.
那是我的专长
That's my thing.
还有那个证据 那个神奇填上的字谜
And this proof, this mysteriously filled in
很明显就是你自己填的
crossword, could very easily have been you.
我没填
I didn't fill it in.
不 只是你不知道而已
No. You don't know you filled it in.
你还不知道你晚上睡觉的时候会说什么
You also don't know that you talk in your sleep.
鸡蛋
Eggs.
你在说什么
What are you saying?
你是说我睡觉的时候把字谜解开了
Are you saying I sleep crossword?
我是说这个的可能性最大
I'm saying it makes more sense than the alternative.
我知道你在干嘛了
I get what you're doing.
我在干嘛
What am I doing?
你不想还有希望见到埃琳娜
You refuse to have hope that you'll see Elena again
没希望就不会失望
so you don't have to be disappointed.
我不想有希望是因为根本就没有
I refuse to have hope because there's nothing to hope for.
猪肉皮
Pork rinds.
不在清单上 而且很恶心
Not on the list and eww.
不 达蒙
No, Damon.
之前架子上放了有猪肉皮的
There were pork rinds here on this shelf.
每一次我们来购物 架子上都放了有猪肉皮
There have been pork rinds here on every shopping trip we've had
这四个月以来都有
for the past 4 months.
你听到了吗
You hear that?
嗯
Hmm.
你听到了吗 达蒙
You hear that, Damon?
那就是希望的声音
That's what hope sounds like.
这个医院牌子 看来改头换面了 对吧
This hospital thing, it's a whole new look, huh?
是啊 很显然这颜色掩饰了
Yeah. Apparently this color disguises
每天覆盖着我的身体液体
all bodily fluids that I could get covered in throughout the day.
至今为止 基本上都还在处于观察期
So far, it's been mostly observation,
但 我不知道 我喜欢那里
but... I don't know... I love it there.
看着病人一点点痊愈 让人很鼓舞
Seeing sick people getting better, it's inspiring.
你看起来不同了 你看起来 额 更快乐了
You seem different. You seem, um, happier.
那你呢 你快乐吗
And you? Are you happy?
卡罗琳告诉了我一点东西
Caroline filled me in a little bit.
噢  关于 那个 地狱的晚宴
Oh. About the, uh, dinner party from hell.
同样是她的原话
Her exact words actually.
在那些夸夸其谈中间 她可能提到了
And in between the ranting, she may have mentioned
一些新工作和新女友的事情
something about a new job and a new girlfriend.
艾薇 对吗 是叫艾薇吗
Ivy, right? Is it Ivy?
斯特凡 没事的 说真的
Stefan, it's fine. Seriously.
这并不尴尬 我保证
It's not weird, I promise.
我只是很高兴终于见到你了 你知道吗
I'm just happy to finally see you again, you know?
这几个月以来 失去邦妮真的是让人很难熬
It's been really rough losing Bonnie the last couple of months...
对着一个失去哥哥的人来说这事
Which is an incredibly insensitive thing to say
也太不合适了
to somebody who just lost their brother.
我 对不起
I'm... I'm sorry.
不 我也一直在试着从中走出来
No. I've been working on the healing thing, too,
我想是的
I guess.
嘿 额 顺便问一句 你有卡罗琳的消息吗
Hey. Uh, by the way, have you, uh, heard from Caroline?
她没有回复我的电话
She's not returning any of my calls,
我真的很想为我的表现道个歉
and I really want to apologize for the way I acted.
好吧 今天她会在深水湖那边
Well, she'll be there at the swimming hole today.
你应该来
You should come.
不 不 我还不确定我是否准备好
No, no. I'm not sure I'm ready to dive
又跳回到那堆东西
back into all that.
我没有双重意思
No pun intended.
斯特凡 他们也是你的朋友
Stefan, they're your friends, too.
来吧 我知道我们不能像以前在酒吧那样一起玩乐了
Come on. I know that we can't hang out at the grill anymore,
但那并不意味着我们不能
but that doesn't mean we can't all spend
一起打发时间
time together.
来吧 拜托了
Come on, please.
如果不是为了那样 那么至少去说服卡罗琳
If not for that, then at least to convince Caroline that Enzo
恩佐不是新的好朋友的候选人
is not new best friend replacement material.
恩佐也会在那
Will Enzo be there?
是的 但我很轻易就能把他踢走
Yeah, but I can easily uninvite him.
-我更想你来 -不 不用担心
- I'd rather you come. - No. Don't worry about it.
额
Um...
-好吧 也许我会去看看 -很好
- Yeah. Maybe I'll stop by. - Great.
你了解规则了吗
Do you understand the rules?
是啊 规则一 不要提起埃琳娜
Yeah. Rule one... Don't mention Elena
曾经疯狂地爱着达蒙 不然你会杀了我
was madly in love with Damon, or you'll kill me.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
规则二 一点也不要
Rule two... don't really
谈到达蒙 不然你会杀了我
reference Damon at all, or you'll kill me.
没错
Yeah.
-规则三 搽防晒霜 -别拿我开玩笑
- Rule 3... wear sunscreen... - Don't make fun of me.
我们要让埃琳娜过着她想要的 新的快乐的
It's important that we let Elena live her new happy,
无视问题的僵尸生活 这很重要
problem-ignoring zombie life the way she wants.
这真是一句听起来又支持又有意见的奇怪句子
A sentence which sounded oddly supportive and judgmental.
我支持她 她做了她需要做的事
I support her. She did what she needed to do
去停止撕咬无辜路人的行为
to stop chomping on innocent people on the road,
但这不等于我享受
but it doesn't mean that I'm enjoying
独自泡在痛苦的感觉
marinating all alone in my misery.
好吧 我和你一起泡着
Well, I'll marinate with you.
谢谢你这句话 真的
I appreciate it. Really, I do.
但我不是斯特凡
But I'm not Stefan.
规则四 不要再提起那个混蛋的名字 不然
Rule number 4... don't ever mention that jerk's name again, or...
不然你会杀了我 我明白
Or you'll kill me. Got it.
哇哦 那是血还是派的污渍
Whoa! Is that blood or pie?
请你告诉我是派
Please say pie.
噢 那是 额
Oh. That would be, uh...
雪莉 一个菜单上没有的特别菜品
Shirley, a special off-the-menu item.
这顿小晚餐的味道保持得真好啊
This little diner is surprisingly well-stocked.
告诉我你已经抢来了 吃了 擦除记忆了
Tell me that you snatched, ate, erased.
那真是有趣的事
Funny thing about that.
你很好地做了前两件事 第三件事就不必要了
You do the first two properly, the third isn't necessary.
-你杀了她吗 -哦 别表现得那么惊讶
- You killed her? - Oh, don't act all shocked.
好吧 不好意思 死亡总是让我很惊讶
Well, I'm sorry, but death shocks me,
而且还会带来一份失踪人口报告
and it also leads to a missing persons report,
-然后又带来 -警官的调查吗
- which leads to... - A sheriff's investigation?
我好怕怕哦
I'm terrified.
我已经被警告三次了 再有一次 就有惩罚了
I already have 3 warnings. One more, it's a fine.
这里应该会有一条短的错误的电线之类的
It's got to be a short, faulty wiring, something.
或者是有人放了一个硬币进去就打开了
Or someone put a quarter in it and turned it on.
你知道吗 我对这些寄托错地方的希望有些疑惑
You know, I'm a little confused with all this misplaced hope.
好吧 就说有人在这吧
All right. Let's just say there's someone here.
你怎么知道我们会出的去
How do you know we're gonna get out?
你说过这就是你的地狱 对吗
Well, you say that this is your hell, right?
如果有其他人在这 那就表明这不是你的地狱
If there's someone else here, that means it's not your hell,
如果这不是你的地狱 那就表明是外婆放我们到这的
and if it's not your hell, that means grams put us here,
如果是外婆放我们到这的 那就会有出去的路
and if grams put us here, there's a way out.
那只是你自己绕进去的一套逻辑怪圈
There's a hell of a logic knot you've tied for yourself.
谢谢 所以现在我们已经
Thank you. So now that we've
放置好我们的希望 开始玩游戏吧
properly placed our hope, let's play a game.
当我们出了去
When we get out,
你会首先和埃琳娜说什么
what's the first thing you're gonna tell Elena?
抱歉我杀死了邦妮
Sorry I killed Bonnie,
但她是世上
but she was the most annoying person
最讨人烦的人
in the world.
她关不上她的嘴 话说个不停
She wouldn't shut up. She just kept talking.
我是说 只要我杀了邦妮那我就创造了一个奇迹
I mean, it's a wonder I made it as long as I did,
但是事情是这样子的 我觉得这样更好
but here's the thing. I think it's better this way
因为她没有了魔法 并且她一无是处
because she didn't have magic, and she was pretty much useless.
达蒙 怎么了
- Damon. - What?
我不知道 你仍然觉得我一无是处
I don't know. You still think I'm useless?
那不是我的车么
That's my car.
那就是我的车
That's my car!
她是个坚定的人但是很甜美
She's determined but sweet,
是个永恒的乐天派 从不忘记生日
eternal optimist, never forgets a birthday.
还有其它的吗
What else?
从不放弃她的朋友
Never gives up on her friends.
没错 她非常的忠心
Yes. True. She's completely loyal.
不错啊  你们这么捧她
This is good. Build her up.
我确定她会活在那些荒唐的很高的期望中
I'm sure she'll live up to these ridiculously high expectations.
还有一个
That's another one.
那就是她善于超出所有的期望
Great at surpassing expectations.
那她很完美啊 完完全全地
- So she's perfect. - Totally.
几乎完美
Pretty much.
那么你们俩在一起多久了
So how long have you two been together?
我们 不 我们只是 额
Us? No. I'm... we're... heh.
我们没在一起 我是说 过去我们确实在一起过
We're not, but, I mean, we did at one point...
再也回不去咯
Not anymore.
是最近分的手么
Was that recent?
因为你们俩看起来怪怪的
Because you two seem weirdly functional.
已经过去两年了吧
Has it already been two years?
岁月如梭啊
Time flies.
我们还要听你呜呜多久啊
How much longer are we gonna listen...
嘘 别出声
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
这声音比你的嗓音好听不知多少
This sound is the opposite sound of your voice,
所以我很喜欢
and I so enjoy it.
这辆车怎么会在这里的 达蒙 是你在1994年把它留在这的吗
How did it even get here, Damon? Did you leave it here in 1994?
我不知道 邦妮 那是18年前的事了
I don't know, Bonnie. It was 18 years ago.
那天我可是很忙的
Has a lot going on that day.
好吧 所以你就承认这不大可能是你留下的
Ok. So you admit that it's pretty unlikely that you did.
非常不可能
Very unlikely.
那么显而易见 就是
Which would stand to reason that...
有人把车停在了这里 邦妮
Someone may have put it here, Bonnie.
没错 额
Yes. I...
达蒙
Damon...
我知道
I know.
我要告诉埃琳娜我有多爱她
I'm gonna tell Elena how much I love her,
然后我会向她道歉因为我杀了你
and then I'm gonna apologize for killing you.
等等 你刚才看到了吗
Wait. Did you see that?
当然看到了
I did that time.
让我们会会我们的小伙伴
Let's go meet our little friend.
这是一个不同于深水湖的湖 还是
So is a lake different from a swimmin' hole, or...
是深水湖
Swimming hole.
谢谢你让我听到乡下人一样的发音
Thanks for making me sound like a redneck.
为什么 你们在高中时都在哪开派对
Why? Where did you party in High School?
在一些人的家里或者别墅里
Oh. Somebody's house or second house,
无论哪一处都有一个很大的湖
whichever had the biggest pool.
恩 我觉得我在吹嘘
Huh. I guess I do brag.
没错 那么轮到我来吹嘘一下了
Yup. Now it's my turn to brag
因为我打赌在你的池边派对上没人能做到这个
because I bet nobody at your pool parties could do this.
咳
Ahem.
额 咳咳 杰瑞米
Um, ahem. Jeremy?
我的天
Oh, my God.
埃琳娜
Elena.
抱歉在我看来你们正在为爱
Sorry to interrupt what I'm sure was
真情流露时打扰了你们
a heartfelt display of true love,
但我是杰瑞米的姐姐
but I'm Jeremy's sister,
并且我们正打算进行一次小小的家庭对话
and we were about to have a nice little family chat.
这就是为什么我是一个快乐的孤儿
That's why I'm an happy orphan.
你邀请了那个被我攻击过的女孩
You invited the girl that I attacked?
不是 我带的是被卡罗琳催眠忘记你攻击过她的那个女孩
No. I brought the girl Caroline compelled to forget you attacked.
她什么都不知道
She doesn't know anything.
杰瑞米 你为什么要冒这个险
- Jer, why would you even risk it?
因为她穿比基尼看上去不错
- Because she looks good in a bikini.
我能走了吗
Can I go now?
我可能会开车载你 但是如果你吐在我的车里
Yeah. I may be driving, but if you puke in my truck,
那么你就死定了
I'm gonna kill you.
你看 那个狗咬过的女孩真辣
You know, dog bite girl's kind of hot
尽管看起来感觉非常的蹩脚
in, like, a trashy way, though.
为什么你一直叫她狗咬的女孩
Why do you keep calling her that... dog bite girl?
因为这很荒唐 什么样的狗
Because it's ridiculous. What kind of dog
会咬在人的脖子上
bites you in the neck.
我不知道 伙计
I don't know, man
我见过一些凶猛的狗
I've seen some pretty vicious dogs.
怎么了 泰勒
What's up, Ty?
我刚收到埃琳娜的短信 她想见我们
I just got a text from Elena. She wants to see us.
等等
Hold on.
你是想告诉我一个女孩脖子上的两处
Are you telling me that you think a girl
刺破的孔一样的伤口
with two puncture wounds in her neck
是被狗咬的吗
got bit by a dog?
我觉得她说什么就是什么
I think if that's what she said then that's what happened.
那么你就是个白痴
Then you're an idiot.
那你也是个无用的人渣
And you're a wasted douchebag.
我们都有过错
We all have faults.
你敢说大声点吗
You want to say that a little louder?
杰 退后
Jay, back off.
不不不 我觉得你刚才叫我人渣
No, no, no. I think you just called me a douchebag.
我只是想确认一下
I just want to make sure.
喂 杰 杰 你现在做的事
Whoa, Jay! Jay, what you're doing right now,
就是人渣做的事
definition of a douchebag.
嘿 憋着啊
Heh. Simmer.
我只是玩玩的
I'm just playing.
你们想来些啤酒吗
You guys want beers?
好啊
Yeah.
抱歉
Sorry.
嗨 我是斯特凡嘟声后请留言
Stefan on phone: Hey. It's Stefan. Leave a message.
没错 不回电就是他的新事物的其中之一
Yeah. Not answering is one of his new things.
他说过他会来着道歉的
He said he was here to apologize.
说谎也是他的新习惯之一
Lying. Also one of his new things.
斯特凡有很多的新习惯
Stefan has a lot of new things.
嗨 你们见到斯特凡了吗
Hey. Have you guys seen Stefan?
我都不知道他回来了
I didn't even know he was back.
你让我们知道来这做什么
So you want to fill us in on what we're doing here?
你不记得这个地方了吗
You don't remember this place?
过去当我们的父母在外边烧烤的时候
We used to sneak off here and get wasted
我们常常溜这来而且喝的醉醺醺
while our parents were outside grilling.
就算 我们都没什么父母
Granted, we all have a few less parents,
但是我们仍然能玩的开心
but we can still have fun.
事实上 我不能
Actually, I can't.
我正在处理我的狂怒问题 这帮不上什么忙
I'm working on my rage issues, and this wouldn't help.
我朋友醉了 而且我早上已经训练过了 所以
My buddy's wasted, and I've got to train in the morning, so...
好吧 我不想让自己听起来像个酒鬼
Ok. Well, I don't want to sound like an alcoholic,
但我想尝试一下 那么有人和我做一次吗
but I do want a shot, so will someone do one with me?
我来
Done!
干杯 恩
Bottoms up. - Mmm!
好了 我们来了
Well... Here we are,
玩的很愉快
having fun.
我玩的很愉快 难道我们玩的不愉快吗
I'm having fun. Aren't we having fun?
这真的很好玩
This is really fun.
好吧 很显然 这真是个大错误
Ok. Clearly, this was a big mistake.
我只是想花一个下午
I just wanted to spend one afternoon
假装我们并没有渐渐疏远
where we pretend for just one second
一秒钟就够了
like we're not all drifting apart.
好吧 问题就在这 埃琳娜
Well, that's the problem, Elena.
不是我们之中的所有人都会不介意假装
Not all of us are ok with pretending.
我们中的一些人情愿面对我们迎头而来的问题
Some of us prefer to face our problems head-on.
我觉得我们该走了 没错
- I think we should go. - Yeah.
怎么回事
What's going on?
我只是孤单了
I'm just lonely, ok?
而且邦妮走了 斯特凡走了
And Bonnie's gone, Stefan's gone.
恩佐 是个令人震惊 可怕的 凶残的朋友
Enzo... shocker... Terrible, murderous friend.
我仍然在这 卡洛琳
I'm still here, Car.
恩
Yeah.
你还在这里
You're still here.
来 再干一杯
Here take another shot and...
好吧 还不如不说
Ok. Not so much.
它在那个小卡车后面 不 在它前面
- It was behind the pickup. - No. It was in the front.
你确定吗 完全确定
- Are you sure? - Yes. Absolutely I'm sure.
它就在那儿
It was right there.
是块油布
It was a tarp.
我们看到了一块油布
We saw a tarp.
还有那个 是设置了时间的
And that... that is on a timer.
到时间会自己启动
That turned on by itself.
但是你的车
But your car.
我94年的时候把它留在这了
I left it here in '94.
-那个字谜 -是你填的 邦妮
- And the crossword? - You filled it out, Bonnie.
我们是这里仅有的两个人
Which means we're alone in my own hell
没有任何机会逃出去
with no grams escape hatch.
我们出不去了
We're never getting out.
-把你的戒指给我 -干嘛
- Give me your ring. - What?
把你的戒指给我
Give me your ring.
你老是说你的人生没有希望了
All I've heard you say is that you have no hope
你身处地狱
and that this is your hell,
如果真的是这么惨 为什么你不自行了断呢
so if it's so bad, why don't you just end it?
希望是支持我走下去的唯一动力 达蒙
Hope is the only thing keeping me going, Damon,
所有你真的觉得自己死定了 没有希望了
so if you're really done, if you have none,
那就去死吧
then be done
在这抱怨根本没用
because this isn't helping.
真是艰难的一天 是不是 达蒙
Rough day, huh, Damon?
不好意思 忘记了礼数 我是凯
Sorry. Manners. I'm Kai.
见到你很高兴
Nice to meet you.
吃猪皮吗
Pork rind?
你确定你能找到回家的路
So you're sure you're ok to find your way back home?
抱歉 我的朋友卡罗琳她最近
Sorry. My friend Caroline's having
有一些麻烦缠身
a bit of a crisis.
这几个月对她来说很难过
It's been a rough couple of months for her.
她平常很好人的
She's normally really sweet.
说真的 我很庆幸没见到她
Actually, I'm glad I didn't meet her
要不然我这么做的时候
because then it would have been awkward
就会很尴尬了
when I did this.
亲一个为你和
Heh. Kissing a girl who's
闺蜜搭线的女生
trying to set you up with her best friend?
这样做不是很好哦
Red flag.
也许吧 我感觉
Maybe. I have a sneaking suspicion
我是你喜欢的类型
that's your type.
这些冰是给卡罗琳的
That was Caroline's ice.
是嘛 反正你都要死了
Yeah. Well, you'll be dead,
她应该不会怪你
so I think she'll let you off the hook.
我不想杀你 斯特凡
I don't want to kill you, Stefan.
啊
Unh!
但是他似乎是想的
But it looks like he did.
我以为我叫了恩佐去拿冰来了
I thought I told Enzo to go get more ice.
你就是用这种语气跟他说的吗
Did you do it in that tone?
那我知道他为什么没有了
Because I think I know why he didn't.
恭喜你 现在这是你的事了
Congratulations. Now it's your job.
去拿些冰来
Go get ice.
我们不是来找乐子的吗
Aren't we supposed to be having fun?
所以你把你最新泡上
Is that why you brought your latest fling
的妹子带到这来
in a series of sad attempts
假装你已经忘了邦妮
to pretend like you don't care about Bonnie...
来找乐子吗
To have fun?
好了 后援来了
Right. Cavalry's on their way,
我们暂停一下小打小闹
so why don't we put a pin in our little spat
把这个解决了再继续怎么样
till this all gets sorted, eh?
不用了 谢谢
No, thanks.
你特么肯定是在逗我
You've got to be bloody kidding me.
我刚刚救了你
I just saved your life.
所以你才可以让我一辈子痛苦
So you can give me a lifetime full of misery.
没关系 我把一辈子缩短点好了
Well, that's fine. I'm just gonna shorten the lifetime.
斯特凡
Stefan.
好消息 卡罗琳 我干掉了一个吸血鬼猎人
Good news, Caroline. I thwarted a vampire hunter.
坏消息是 斯特凡变成吸血鬼猎人了
Bad news... Stefan has become a vampire hunter.
你在干嘛
What are you doing?
你怎么不问他呢
Why don't you ask him?
你做了什么
What did you do?
你必须停下来
That is gonna have to stop.
哦 你觉得这声音很讨厌
Oh, you think this is annoying?
那你得去听听你和邦妮每隔五分钟就会有一次的吵架
Hmm. Try listening to you and Bonnie bicker every 5 minutes.
-所以你一直在跟踪我们 -当然了
- So you've been following us. - Of course I have.
看你们俩吵架是我最接近看电视的活动了
You two are the closest thing I have a to a TV.
你们不是海岸救生队 但是
I mean, you're no "Baywatch," But...
-记得海岸救生队吗 -不记得
- Remember "Baywatch"? - No, I do not.
哦 你必须去看看
Oh. Oh, man, you got to watch it.
你就像救生员 很有魅力的那类
You like lifeguards, like... Hot ones?
今天是这么多糟糕的日子以来
This has been a monumentally bad day
最糟糕的一天 所以我要你
in a sea of bad days, so I'm gonna need
告诉我你是谁 在这做什么
to know who you are, what you're doing here,
跟我有什么关系
and how it relates to me,
否则我就撕破你的喉咙
or I'm gonna rip your throat out.
脾气会坏你大事的 达蒙
Temper's gonna get you in trouble, Damon.
你都气走邦妮多少次了
It's already driven Bonnie away how many times?
哦 等等 我知道 十三次
Oh, oh, oh, wait. I know. 13.
你以为我对她发脾气吗
You think my temper's bad with her?
我喜欢她
I like her.
但是你嘛 就不怎么喜欢了
You not so much.
好吧 好吧 对不起 我很认真
Ok. Ok. Sorry. Seriously.
我只是对处理面对面交流
I'm just kind of rusty
有点生疏了
on the face-to-face type human interactions.
回答我的问题 马上
Answers now.
也许你应该喝一口
Maybe you should have a drink.
通常能使你冷静下来
That usually calms you down.
谢谢
Thanks.
然后你又会生气 之后是沮丧
Then makes you angry, then sad,
最后又会冷静下来
then calm again.
是个奇怪的循环 听着
It's a weird cycle, and look,
如果你真的想知道我为什么跟踪你们
if you really want to know the reason I'm following you,
因为我想杀了你
it's because I want to kill you.
马鞭草在你的体内沸腾
Vervain in your bourbon.
现在不知道是谁要遭殃了
Who didn't see that one coming?
谁会去杂货铺买露台家具
Who buys patio furniture from a grocery store?
一定是有人去了
I mean, somebody must.
否则的话 它不会出现在这里的
Otherwise, it... it wouldn't be here,
我不是很了解吸血鬼
but now I'm a little unfamiliar with vampires,
但从我收集到的资料
but from what I've gathered,
把木桩插入心脏就行了 对吧
a stake in the heart should do it, right?
啊
Aah!
你一直在耍肮脏手段 达蒙
You can always fight dirty, Damon.
就像那次你跟邦妮玩独占游戏
Like that time you and Bonnie played monopoly
你从银行里偷钱一样
and you stole from the bank.
一点都不酷
Not cool.
我要把你的头扭下来 -不 你不会的
- I'm gonna rip your head off. - No. You're not.
我不知道你会拿哪瓶酒
I didn't know which bottle you'd take,
所以我全部都加了马鞭草
so I vervained them all.
离他远点
Stay away from him.
没用的人来了
The useless one is here.
感谢上帝
Thank God.
这几个月我一直看着你试图施展魔法
I've watched you try to do magic for months now.
你要做什么 阻止我吗
What are you gonna do, fail at me?
真难堪
It's embarrassing.
我为你感到难堪
I'm embarrassed for you.
呃 哦
Uh-oh.
快跑
Run.
【咒语】
Phesmatos.
火焰
Incendia.
好了 好了 好了
Ok. Ok. Ok.
这么快就弃械投降了
Giving up so soon?
我为你感到难堪
I'm embarrassed for you.
抱歉我称呼你为世界上最讨人烦的人
Sorry I called you the most annoying person in the world.
那时我还没见到他
I hadn't met him yet.
哇哦 那个一直都是凹的吗
Whoa. Was that always dented?
有什么关系 这只是个桶子
What the hell does it matter? It's a keg.
丽芙借给我的
Liv lent them to me man.
哦 在你把你的男子气概借给丽芙的时候
Oh, is that when you lent Liv your manhood?
抬上来吧
Just lift the damn thing.
事实上 不用了
Actually, don't.
我急需一辆空车箱
I'm in desperate need of an empty truck bed.
这不是你的朋友 杰 吗
Isn't this your friend Jay?
你做了什么
What the hell did you do?
我躲过了他打算用来杀死我和斯特凡的木桩
I avoided the stake he planned to fire at Stefan and me.
木桩
Stake?
恩 你不知道你的朋友是个吸血鬼猎人吗
Ah. You didn't realize your friend was a vampire hunter?
那现在你知道了
Well, you do now.
不 不 不 那不可能
No. No, no. That's not possible.
事实就是如此
Yes, it is,
我越来越想看着你一步步知道
and as much as I'd like to watch you process
那些可怕的真相了
what I'm sure is a dreadful revelation,
我得埋了这具尸体
I need to bury the body.
我们走吧
Get out of here.
斯特凡
Stefan!
别走 好吗 对不起
Stop, ok? I am sorry.
-我不知艾薇的事情 但是 -但是什么
- I did not know about Ivy, but... - But what? What?
我在自欺欺人 用她来逃避现实
I was fooling myself, I was using her as an escape?
是 我知道你在想什么 卡罗琳
Yeah, I know what you think, Caroline.
好吧 我其实是想说
Well, actually, I was gonna say,
但是 杀了恩佐能让她起死回生
"But killing Enzo won't bring her back."
不能 但杀了他能阻止他让我想起我哥
No, but it will stop him from reminding me of my brother.
杀了他 我就能离开这里
I kill him, I can leave this place,
我能重新开始
and I can start over again.
所以 这就是你给我发信息
So that's why you left all those messages on my phone,
诚恳地道歉的原因
promising apologies.
这就是你去找埃林娜的原因
That's why you visited Elena,
你来参加派对的原因
that's why you came to this party,
只是为了要杀恩佐 然后重新开始生活
just to kill Enzo and start over?
没错
Yep.
我不相信
I don't believe you.
我知道有你心里有个部分想念着这个地方
I know that a part of you misses this place
这里的人 你的朋友
and these people, your friends.
我知道回到这里会让你想起
I know that being back here reminds you
我们有多么需要你 我 有多么需要你
how much we need you, how much... I need you,
但如果我错了 那就走吧 离开 重新开始
but if I'm wrong, then go ahead. Just go. Start over,
但 天啊 如果我对了呢
but, God, if I'm right,
如果 有一小部分的你 回来这里
if just a little part of you came back
是为了看看
to check on Elena,
痛苦不堪了四个月的埃林娜
who's had an unbearable 4 months,
或者是刚刚死而复生的阿拉里克
or Alaric, who just came back from the dead,
或者是我
or me...
就算是你回来只有一点点 一点点
If even just a small, little part of you
是为了看看我
came back to check on me...
那就留下来
Then stay.
嘿 你没拿到冰块吗
Hey. Weren't you getting ice?
我刚刚才意识到那个女孩对我有多恶劣
I was till I realized how mean that girl was to me.
-有多恶劣 -嗯 我是有自尊的
- How? - Um, I have self-respect.
虽然直到我在去酒水服务处的半路上
It may have taken me till I was halfway to the sip and serve
我才意识到 但我是有自尊的
to realize it, but I have it.
等等 去酒水服务处的半路上
Wait. Halfway to the sip and serve?
那是在哪个位置
Where is that specifically?
我不知道 进神秘瀑布镇
I don't know. Right around route 13
第13路附近吧
when you get into Mystic Falls.
很抱歉没能给你的酒降温
Sorry about your warm booze.
-有见到莎拉吗 没有 怎么了
- Have you guys seen Sarah? - No. Why?
-没有冰块了 我想没有冰块你也可以的 杰里米
- There's no ice. - I think you'll live, Jer.
卡罗琳强制催眠那个女孩去拿冰块 但她没有
Caroline compelled that girl to go get ice. She didn't.
为什么没有 她碰到马鞭草了吗
Well, why not? Is she on vervain?
没有 她有去神秘瀑布镇要去拿冰块
No. She had to go into Mystic Falls to get it.
-她穿过了边界 强制催眠可是魔法啊
- She had to cross the border. - Compulsion is magic.
这意味着所有你强制催眠让人忘记的记忆
Which means that every memory you compelled away
都恢复了 所有 莎拉 你攻击
came back, so Sarah, the girl you attacked
你催眠的那个女孩
and you compelled...
知道我是什么了
Knows what I am.
你醒了 很好
You're awake. Good.
现在是今晚的问答环节了
Now for the Q&A portion of the evening.
让我猜猜 我答对了
Let me guess. I answer right,
给我块猪皮
I get a pork rind.
答错了 给我一棍
Wrong, I get a poker.
什么 不 不 不
What? No, no, no.
这些是给我吃的
These are for me.
你只有挨棍子的份
You just get the poker.
-你没必要这么做 -没有吗
- Yeah. You don't have to do that. - No?
-我们是同一阵营的 -真的吗
- We're on the same team. - Really?
你经常坑杀队友的吗
Do you always try and kill your teammates?
重要的是你的魔力回来了
The important thing is that you have your magic back.
我的方法有用
It worked.
你不会真的以为
What, you... you didn't really think
我会杀了达蒙吧
I'd kill Damon, did you?
哈哈 这怎么有可能
Heh heh. In what universe does that make sense?
谁会这么蠢杀了我们三人中的一个
Who would kill 1/3 of our population?
我又不是禽兽
I'm not a monster.
我知道邦妮会出现
I knew Bonnie would show up.
她总是会回来的 十三次都是
She always comes back, all 13 times,
我知道只要刺激到位了
and I knew with the right motivation
她就会重获魔力
she'd be able to access her magic,
虽然我有点担心
although I-I did get a little worried
你们吵了这么多次
with all your bickering that
用达蒙的生命作威胁可能不够
Damon's life wouldn't be enough motivation,
但是竟然可以
but turns out it was.
我想这也说明了你们之间的感情
I guess that's just how you two show your love.
所以你做了这一切就是为了让我重获魔力
So you did all that just to make sure I would have my magic?
当然啦
Of course I did.
因为你的魔力是我们离开这的关键
Because your magic is the key to getting the hell out of here.
也许这是单一事件而已
Maybe this is an isolated thing.
杰可能是单干
Jay could be working alone.
是啊 可能是杰 我十岁就认识他了
Yeah. Maybe Jay, who I've known since I was 10,
但是他现在却变成了吸血鬼猎人
somehow became a vampire hunter on his own.
我真是蠢
I'm such an idiot.
整个夏天我都在和创始人家族的人一起训练
I spent all summer training with a founding family member,
以为他只是担心
thinking that he was only worried
想保护老奶奶不被抢劫
about protecting old ladies from getting mugged.
这就是我想过的星期六晚生活
Because this is how I wanted to spend my saturday night.
把东西装上来
Load them up.
你们的车到底是怎么了
What the hell happened to your truck anyway?
说来话长
It's a little complicated.
我来搞定 等会去找你
I got this, dude. I'll see you in a bit.
伤心的运动员有点像伤心的小丑
Sad jocks are kind of like sad clowns,
你知道 很可悲却也有点好笑
you know, they're pathetic but kind of hilarious.
现在没心情说这个 丽芙
Not in the mood, Liv.
听起来像是威胁
Uh-oh. That sounded like a threat.
不 只是个请求
No. Just a request.
好吧
Oops.
你真的想这么做
Is this what you want?
你想看到我爆发
You want to see my break?
你说的对 抱歉
You're right. I'm sorry.
对我来说你变成一只
It's just easier for me if you're
攻击性的不讨喜动物会比较容易
an aggressive unlikable dick.
为什么
Why?
这样我就不用担心会喜欢上你了
So I don't have to worry about falling for you.
每个房间都检查过了 萨拉走了
I checked every room. Sarah is gone,
看起来她好像把整个房子变成了垃圾堆
and it looks like she trashed the place.
好吧
Oh, ok, ok.
卡罗琳和我会
Where Caroline and I will, uh,
出去在边界那里找一找
go out and search near the border then.
我会继续在镇里面找的
I'll keep looking in town.
有什么发现我会告诉你的
I'll call you if I find anything.
我打算在我们出去找的过程中
So I was just gonna leave my clothes here
把衣服放在这 如果你不介意的话
while we look, if that's ok.
好啊 当然可以
Yeah. Of course.
我在想 你也知道
I also was thinking that, you know,
如果真的有吸血鬼猎人在活动的话
if there are vampire hunters on the loose
独自一人住在他们地下室旁边
then living alone right by their home base
可能不是很好
is probably not a good idea.
这是正式住下来的意思吗
Is this an official unpack?
因为我不太理解你的意思
Because your moving methods are just so confusing.
是 这是正式住下来的意思
Yes, this is an official unpack.
啊
Ha!
我很抱歉之前对你发脾气了
I'm sorry I got mad at you earlier.
有时候只是忍不住 你好像
Sometimes, it just seems like you have
有可以开始新生活的秘诀
this secret way to move on.
-这是 -邦妮的吗
- Is this... - Bonnie's?
是
Yeah.
就是这个了
There you go.
你发现了我开始新生活的秘诀
You just discovered my secret to moving on.
有些时候 我做不到
Sometimes, I don't.
我想念邦妮
I miss Bonnie.
想念神秘瀑布镇
I miss Mystic Falls,
想念过去的一切
I miss our old life,
-想念 -斯特凡
- I miss... - Stefan?
是啊 想念斯特凡
Yeah. I miss Stefan.
卡罗琳
Caroline...
你和斯特凡
You and Stefan...
你是不是喜欢他还是怎样
Do you have feelings for him or something?
我想我可能是吧
Yeah, I think maybe I did.
好吧 我们应该出发了 去找那个女生
Well, we should go ahead and find that girl
得赶在她摆脱我们之前
before she outs us.
难过的一晚
Rough night?
啊 这不是一块蛋糕就能弥补的
Ahh. Nothing a piece of pie can't fix.
有人来帮忙倒酒水我感激不尽
Service would be lovely, though.
是我的错 抱歉
My fault. Sorry.
我叫大家回去了
I sent everyone home for the night.
不能再让你杀酒保了
Can't have you killing any more of the wait staff.
啊
Unh!
喝血的时候小心点
Consider being more discreet when you feed.
因为你不知道有谁会看着你
You never know whose eyes are watching.
我相信这个通常会起作用 是不是
I bet this normally works, doesn't it?
能让吸血鬼昏迷
Knocks vampires right out.
看到了吗 我和普通的吸血鬼不一样
See, I'm a bit different than a normal vampire.
我可以抵抗马鞭草的效用 不是很久
I can fight the vervain, not for long, but...
够时间解决你了
Long enough to take care of you.
我在你们当中的一人身上找到这个
I found this on one of your guys.
我相信是被他杀了的
I think he killed him, though.
-你是谁 -斯特凡 萨瓦托尔
- Who are you? - Stefan Salvatore.
你和我有相似之处
You and I have something in common.
都是来自创始人家族 谢谢
One of the founding families. Thank you.
其实 如果你不介意的话
Actually... If you don't mind,
我有偏好的杀死他们的方式
I have my own way I like them to die.
让他们死得痛苦点就行了
Just make sure it's painful.